# ROBERT ISAAC EBITA CORTEZ

Front End Web Developer

South Cotabato, Philippines

+63 985 652 8649

☑ isaacebitacortez@gmail.com



#### **ABOUT ME**

As a former student nurse turned web developer, Isaac's resume highlights his transferable skills from nursing education and business administration, such as problem-solving, communication, and presentation skills, secretarial experience, volunteer work, current education and skills in web development, and personal projects and achievements.

#### SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Canva

Presentation Skills, Counseling Skills, Clerical Skills, Problem-Solving Skills, Graphic Design Skills

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Outlook, Powerpoint)

#### LINKS

### LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/robert-isaac -ebita-cortez-376320310

### GitHub

https://github.com/lsaacCortezUIU Χ

### E-Portfolio

https://isaacuiux.netlify.app/

### LANGUAGES

English

Filipino

Hiligaynon

### HOBBIES

Interested in Rock Climbing, Graphic Design, Manga,

### COURSEWORK

#### Sydney, NSW, Australia **NURSING COURSEWORK**

- completed coursework in Anatomy, Physiology, Epidemiology, Patient Care, and Mental Health Nursing at University of Technology Sydney - enhanced skills in communication and critical thinking skills

### Online

### INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

- completed coursework in Basic Programming and Information Literacy at Mapua Malayan Digital College
- enhanced skills in analysis, logic and critical thinking

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

RS Cortez: Fresh & Frozen South Cotabato

#### FEB 2018 - FEB 2019

#### **SECRETARY**

- · Managed administrative tasks for a family business specializing in wholesale delivery of seafood goods.
- · Coordinated orders and deliveries of commercial seafood products, including salmon, milkfishes, and yellowfin tuna.
- · Handled customer inquiries and ensured timely and accurate delivery of goods.
- · Developed strong organizational and clerical skills in a fast-paced business environment.

Various Hospitals Sydney

#### DEC 2020 - MAY 2021

#### STUDENT NURSE PLACEMENTS

- Bankstown Hospital (Stroke and Rehabilitation): Assisted in patient care and rehabilitation programs for geriatric stroke patients (Bankstown NSW, December 2020)
- · Bankstown Hospital (Endocrinology): Supported the medical team in managing patients with endocrine disorders (Bankstown NSW, February 2021)
- · Croydon Community Health Centre (Community Mental Health): Participated in community visits and mental health support programs (Croydon, May 2021)

Zion Christian Misson Center Sydney

FEB 2020 - FEB 2023

#### **VOLUNTEER STAFF**

- · Assisted in organizing and coordinating community church events at a branch church.
- · Engaged with community members to foster a welcoming environment.
- · Developed presentation and counseling skills through event participation.
- · Initiated counseling sessions and spiritual discussions with guests
- Scouted potential theology students to study 8–10 month

## **EDUCATION**

**Uplift Code Camp** 

2024

#### Online **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP**

- working towards training and certification as a Full Stack Web Developer
- includes projects and activities utilizing HTML, CSS, Javascript, ReactJS, Tailwind, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB

**UTS College** Sydney

**UTS-COLLEGE FOUNDATION STUDIES** Notre Dame of Marbel University - Integrated Basic Education

2018

2020

Koronadal City, South Cotabato

### HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Department

- Graduated with honors (Average of 91)